

WEB DEVELOPER/ UI DESIGNER

SKILLS

Web

- HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap
- Js JavaScript (DOM, jQuery), React
- PHP et Symfony 4
- Ruby on Rails
- MySQL, PostgreSQL

Design & CMS

- Ps Photoshop
- Wordpress

Tools

- Git & Github
- Figma, Sketch & InVision
- Trello, Slack (Agile
 method, SCRUM,
 Kanban)

INTERESTS

- Travel to South-East Asia (5 months), WHV in Australia
- Guitar, Horse-riding, Basketball, Roller
- Reading (novel, autobiography, history)
- Follow new trends in technology

VIRGINIE LENOIR

06 58 66 55 72

✓ virginie.lenoir17@gmail.com

English: fluent

☐ https://virginie-Inr.github.io

in www.linkedin.com/in/virginie-lenoir

https://github.com/Virginie-Inr

Passionate about technologies and innovation, I started coding in 2019. During these two years of training I acquired a wide range of skills from web development, to project methodology and design. I am know looking for a frontend developer/ UI developer position where I can continue grow my skills.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER - RAKETECH

MAY 2021 - PRESENT | REMOTE MALTA

- Identify the causes of reported issues and implement the respective fixes
- Coordinate with UX/UI designers, developers in an Agile environment

WEB DEVELOPER & DESIGNER (PERSONAL PROJECT) - CREECOLO

FEB TO APRIL 2021 | REMOTE

- Build the MVP of a web application using PHP & Symfony 4
- Agile Project Management (create a list of Backlogs and User Stories on Trello, prioritise and implement the features)
- Build a Website Specification & Prototype the web app using Figma

FULL STACK DEVELOPER - 12.5

JANUARY TO FEBRUARY 2021 | REMOTE PARIS

- Front/Back: Implement new features/pages/fix bugs
- Git/Github: working as a team using versioning control
- SEO: content optimisation, html markup, semantic
- UI/UX design: prototyping on Figma, improve responsive design

SALES OPERATIONS SPECIALIST - REKKI

PERMANENT (FEB 2019 - MARCH 2020 | LONDON)

- Management of the operations internal system:
 - Collaboration with Product Manager and developer to improve our system/ add new functionalities / report and fix minor bugs
 - Test new version before the release and report to the Product Manager
- Management of the french operations and Quality Control
- Suppliers and users on-boarding
- Ensured positive customer experience for over 3000 users

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

FULLSTACK DEVELOPMENT PHP/SYMFONY- DORANCO - BAC+2 LEVEL

SEPT. 2020 TO DEC. 2020 - REMOTE

• Building dynamic websites / SQL and MySQL / Photoshop/ Wordpress

FULLSTACK DEVELOPMENT RUBY ON RAILS - BOOTCAMP (THP)

MARCH 2020 TO JUNE 2020 - REMOTE

- Back-end development with OOP/ Unit testing with Rspec
- Agile Project Management (User stories, Backlogs) / Web design

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN PROJECT DEVELOPMENT & SOCIAL INTERVENTION

HIGHER NATIONAL DIPLOMA IN ANIMATION, SOCIAL AND SOCIOCULTURAL

2014-2015 - VALEDICTORIAN - BAC+3 | UPEC CRÉTEIL

2012-2014 - BAC+2 | PARIS DESCARTES